const quizData = [
    {
      question: " 1) What is the main advantage of using OOP?",
      options: [
        "Faster development",
        "Reusability of code",
        "Easier to learn",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      answer: "Reusability of code"
    },
    {
      question: " 2) Which of the following is not a feature of OOP?",
      options: [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Inheritance",
        "Polymorphism",
        "Compilation"
      ],
      answer: "Compilation"
    },
    {
      question: " 3) What is the process of creating a new class from an existing class called?",
      options: [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Inheritance",
        "Polymorphism",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      answer: "Inheritance"
    },
    {
      question: " 4) Which concept allows you to define methods with the same name but different implementations?",
      options: [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Inheritance",
        "Polymorphism",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      answer: "Polymorphism"
    },
    {
      question: " 5) What is used to hide the internal details of an object?",
      options: [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Inheritance",
        "Polymorphism",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      answer: "Encapsulation"
    },
    {
      question: " 6) Which keyword is used to implement inheritance in Java?",
      options: [
        "extends",
        "implements",
        "inherit",
        "super"
      ],
      answer: "extends"
    },
    {
      question: " 7) Which OOP concept describes the ability of an object to take on many forms?",
      options: [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Inheritance",
        "Polymorphism",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      answer: "Polymorphism"
    },
    {
      question: " 8) Which feature of OOP refers to the bundling of data and methods that operate on the data?",
      options: [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Inheritance",
        "Polymorphism",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      answer: "Encapsulation"
    },
    {
      question: " 9) Which OOP concept allows you to define a blueprint for a class?",
      options: [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Inheritance",
        "Polymorphism",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      answer: "Abstraction"
    },
    {
      question: " 10) Which keyword is used to access the superclass method in the subclass?",
      options: [
        "super",
        "this",
        "extends",
        "parent"
      ],
      answer: "super"
    }
  ];
  
  export default quizData;
  